

KARIN KAY CAPPELLO







Location: London, United Kingdom Phone number: +44 07512070893 Email: karin.kay9@gmail.com

Born and raised in Israel, I moved to Italy to chase my dreams. I've lived there for six years, obtaining three degrees and lots of fun. Currently based in London, I enjoy drawing, reading, and enhancing my skills in product design. Indeed, the quote that best describes my career choice is

"choose a job you love, and you will never have to work a day in your life".

Skills

Photoshop	
Indesign	
Illustrator	
Figma	
Office Suite	
Revit	
Archicad	
Sketchup	
Blender	
Autocad	
HTML	
CSS	
Canva	

Certificates

Visual Elements of User Interface Design / CalArts Fundamentals of Graphic Design / CalArts

Languages

Hebrew Native Language

Full Professional Proficiency English

Italian Partial Proficiency

* Recommendation letters are available upon request.

Work Experience

Sep 2023 - Today Freelancer Product Designer

UX and UI design for mobile applications.

Oct 2022 - Sep 2023 Due Diligence Agent at Wise

Performing customer due diligence and designing an internal

verification tool for a new upcoming product launch.

Apr 2021 - Jun 2021 Architectural Designer at Fuzz Atelier

Detailing and finalisation of public architectural projects.

Feb 2019 - Apr 2019 Architectural Designer at AARCH-MI

Team collaboration in competitions involving urban design.

Sep 2015 - Aug 2016 Ossishkin Elementary School

Assistant to a child with special needs, encouraging his

integration with his classmates.

Apr 2015 - Nov 2016 **Smart Center**

Aug 2012 - Feb 2013 Teacher and tutor. Providing lessons for children of all ages in a

variety of subjects, both individually and in groups.

Mar 2013 - Mar 2015 Israel Defence Forces (IDF) | Home Front Command

> Operation sergeant in a war room, in charge of the alarm system of the country. The task required collaborative team work under a daily pressure and communication with highranked commanders. Received an acknowledgement of excellence and a campaign medal awarded for my participation

in Operation Protective Edge (Miv'tza Tzuk Eitan).

Education

Sep 2019 - Dec 2022 MSc. in Architecture for Sustainability

> Politecnico di Torino Grade: 110 / 110 cum laude

Sep 2019 - Feb 2022 Alta Scuola Politecnica

> A multidisciplinary joint school of Politecnico di Milano and Politecnico di Torino. Students are selected on the basis of merit. Project: Mars-Exos Virtual Reality for Astronauts Training.

Sep 2019 - Oct 2021 MSc. in Architecture - Built Environment - Interiors

> Politecnico di Milano Grade: 110 / 110 cum laude

Aug 2018 - Feb 2019 KEA - Copenhagen School of Design & Technology

Exchange student for one semester.

Oct 2016 - Jul 2019 BSc. in Architectural Design

> Politecnico di Milano Grade: 110 / 110 cum laude

Sep 2009 - Jul 2012 Yigal Alon High School, Israel

Majored in Visual Arts, Psychology and Mathematics. Graduated with honours, at the top of my class.

Extracurricular Activities

May 2019 - May 2021 Student representative elected for the school council at

Politecnico di Milano. [Interview for a promotion video]

Nov 2020 Set Design for <u>'Smudge'</u>. A short film directed by Dor Samara.

Produced by The Steve Tisch School of Film and Television.

Oct 2018 **KEA International Charrette**

> Collaborative development of innovative solutions around the theme of "Connecting Communities - Inclusive Design in the Copenhagen Nordvest District". [Presentation to stakeholders]